Daniel J. Lee

3004 Suncrest Drive, San Diego, CA 92116

<u>Dan.lee619@gmail.com</u> <u>http://DanLee619.github.io</u>

(619) 415-6367

Summary

Well-rounded Cisco Networking Academy graduate with experience working in high-pressure, time-driven environments. Outstanding written and verbal communication skills emphasizing critical analysis and interpersonal collaboration. Exposure to a wide variety of programming languages as well as experience cabling, troubleshooting, and setting up networks. A quick learner who is highly motivated to outperform expectations.

Technical Skills

Routing & Switching: OSPF, EIGRP, RIP, BGP, RSTP, PVST+, ACLs, PAGP/LACP, PPPoE, GRE, IPsec, HSRP, Port-

security Configurations, Spanning tree, VPNs, DHCP, DNS

Programming: Java, Java-script, PHP, MySQL

Web-Design: html5, CSS3

Education

Cisco Networking Academy (2015 - 2016)

BA Degree University of California Santa Barbara (2007 - 2011)

Southwestern College (2013 - 2015)

Mesa College (2013)

Degrees & Certifications

CCNA Certification: Received 2016

Cisco Networking Academy Graduate: Graduated 2016

BA in Film and Media Studies: Emphasis in Media Analysis. Graduated 2011. 3.7 GPA

Work Experience

Team Lead 2014 - Present

The Party Staff Inc.

- Acted as a liaison between clients and home office to resolve any issues that may arise.
- In charge of employees' actions on the job site to ensure that all work is done on or before time and to client's satisfaction.
- Submit event reports and perform other event related data-entry functions
- Personally handle particularly delicate, skill-intensive, or time-sensitive tasks

Marketing and Promotions Assistant

2014 - 2016

Comedy Juice

- Promote upcoming shows via social media.
- Coordinate with local businesses around comedy club
- Canvas surrounding streets before shows to bring in additional customers
- Interact with guests before the show starts to relax their mood and to persuade them to sign up for our weekly mailing list
- Operate the soundboard and lights during the show
- Work with comedians to organize set-times and performance order